creationent.com 2018-12-22

# Creation Entertainment - Supernatural The Television Series - The Vampire Diaries - Star Trek - Stargate SG-1 - Xena - The Twilight Saga - Conventions & Merchandise

www.creationent.com ("Creation Entertainment") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our Web site. The following policy describes how Creation Entertainment seeks to assure its visitors, and the parents of children visiting the site, how it protects information it receives from visitors to the Web site: 

**What information does Creation Entertainment collect and how does Creation Entertainment use it?**

When ordering products on the site, we need you to provide your name, e-mail address, mailing address, and credit card information for purchases. This allows us to verify your order and ship you the information or products desired.

**How does Creation Entertainment protect visitor information?**

Creation Entertainment implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. User personal information is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such information. When you place an order we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information supplied by users is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to be only accessed as stated above.

**Does Creation Entertainment use "cookies"?**

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a Web site can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. Cookies allow Web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor's individual preferences. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major Web sites use them. Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent or notify you whenever you are sent a cookie. This gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access most of the features on the site. Creation Entertainment uses cookies so our shopping cart system can keep track of the contents of your shopping cart.

**Does Creation Entertainment disclose the information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?**

Creation Entertainment does not currently sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any registration, purchase, or e-mail list submission. This information is used to support related transactions made on the site, and to better know our visitors and possibly tailor any specific features, promotions, or other notifications to them.

**Creation Entertainment's special note to parents**

Pursuant to the provisions of the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect information from children under thirteen years of age without the consent of a parent legal guardian. Parent (or legal guardians) may provide us with consent to collect such information by e-mail, by facsimile or by posted mail. Parents may request to review information collected from their child, may ask to have that information deleted, and may refuse to allow further collection or use of the child's information. To request such review or to give instructions regarding the information we have collected about a child, parents/legal guardians should contact us as specified below under "Contact Us".

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children, to participate in the interactive activities offered online, and for children to consult with their parents before submitting any information to this or any other web site. Parents should consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help supervise their children's online activities. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other personal information online without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please consult the "Consumer Assistance" page of the Direct Marketing Association home page.

**How does a visitor opt-out, remove, or modify information they have provided to Creation Entertainment?**

After gathering any user information, Creation Entertainment offers users the opportunity to remove their information from our database so as not to receive future communications or to no longer interact with the Web site until they later chose to. Simply follow the unsubscribe link contained in all e-mail list communications to unsubscribe your e-mail address.

**Third party links**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, Creation Entertainment may choose various third party Web sites to link to from its own site. However, even if the third party is affiliated with Creation Entertainment, Creation Entertainment has no control over these linked sites who each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of Creation Entertainment. Creation Entertainment has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, Creation Entertainment seeks to protect the integrity of its Web site and the links placed upon it and therefore requests any feedback on not only its own site, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work).

**Your consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Creation Entertainment as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Contact Us**

Creation Entertainment welcomes your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to this, or any other issue, at [webmaster@creationent.com](mailto:webmaster@creationent.com). Or you can reach us by posted mail at:

Creation Entertainment  
217 S. Kenwood Street  
Glendale, CA 91205
